panjo.com 2013-12-20

# Privacy

### Privacy Policy

The Panjo.com Website and affiliated Web properties (collectively, the "Website" located at www.Panjo.com) are subject to the following Privacy Policy (the â€œPolicyâ€) and the Terms of Use.

BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, PLEASE EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE.

This Policy was last updated on July 1, 2013.

  1. ### Overview

The Website is owned and operated by Interactive Innovation Group, Inc. a Delaware corporation, and subject to the following Policy. Interactive Innovation Group, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy online. Interactive Innovation Group is referred to herein as â€œIIG,â€ â€œwe,â€ â€œus,â€ and â€œour;â€ the terms â€œyouâ€ and â€œyourâ€ when used in this Policy means any user of the Website.

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post such changes to this Privacy Statement and other places we deem appropriate so you are aware of the information we collect, how we collect it, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will provide registered users with notice of changes to this policy.

Except as limited below, we may use or disclose your information for business reasons in whatever manner as we see fit.

To ensure the highest quality experience, we may use third-parties to operate certain portions of our Website and other services. If you grant permission, information collected from you may be shared with such third-parties.

Except as otherwise provided in this Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you online. For some services, we may collect and/or transfer your information to a third-party. We also may provide links on our Website to unaffiliated third-party websites that may collect and use your personal information according to their privacy policies and terms of use. In those cases, the third-parties will govern how your information is collected and/or used.

  2. ### Information Collected

In order to better provide you with content and access to products and services, we collect two types of information from you: personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to your name, address, and information submitted in creating your Account and Panjo Profile (together â€œPersonally Identifiable Informationâ€) and non-personally identifiable information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide an enjoyable and customized experience while using our Website.

    1. Personally Identifiable Information: We may use Personally Identifiable Information you provide in a limited number of ways. We may use your Personally Identifiable Information to (i) complete a transaction related to a Listing Item, (ii) provide you with information about us, (iii) enhance or update the Website; (iv) review your account to determine whether other Listing Items may be of interest to you; (v) conduct another transaction you request; (vi) compile demographic statistics about our users; (vii) make a record of your visit and log your IP address, the date and time of your visit to the Website, the Listing Items accessed, and the type of browser used; (viii) use in connection with business-related matters. We may also on occasion combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from other parties to enhance our ability to market to you Listing Items that may be of interest to you.

    2. Demographic data also may be collected at our Website through the use of third-party tools. We may review the actions of the visitors of our Website on an aggregate basis to determine customersâ€™ preferences. We also may conduct research on our visitors' demographics, interests, and Listing Items viewed based on the information collected in connection with use of our Website. We may use this data to tailor the visitorâ€™s experience at our Website, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze Website usage, to improve our product offerings, service offerings, and to customize the content, layout, and/or services provided on our Website. We may receive reports from third-party ad servers, content servers, or web site analysis agents that tell us how many ads were presented and clicked upon or what content was served or viewed.

    3. Referral: If you choose to introduce a friend to Panjo, or buy a Listing Item for a friend, we will ask you for your friend's name and/or email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email with the Listing Item you purchased for him or her or inviting him or her to visit the Website. Panjo stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email, sending their Listing Item, and tracking the success of our referral program. A referred friend may contact us at info@panjo.com to request that we remove their information from our database.

    4. Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that does not identify a specific End User. This type of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator (â€œURLâ€) of the website you visited before coming to our Website, the URL of the website you visit after leaving our Website, the type of browser you are using and your Internet Protocol (â€œIPâ€) address. We, and/or our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers, may automatically collect this information when you visit our Website through the use of electronic tools like Cookies and Web beacons or Pixel tags, as described in Items 4 and 8 of this Privacy Policy. This information may also be shared with our authorized third party service providers and advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, and programming. Non-Personally Identifiable Information may also be used to troubleshoot, administer the Website, analyze trends, gather demographic information, comply with applicable laws, and cooperate with law enforcement activities.

Though we will make every effort to preserve user privacy, pursuant to the terms of this Policy, we also may need to disclose Personally Identifiable Information when required by law or if we have a good-faith belief that the action is necessary to comply with a pending judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us or to protect our rights or the rights of others, to fight fraud, identity theft, to ensure the integrity and operation of our business and systems, or to protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, our employees, shareholders or others.

  3. ### Examples of How We Use Collected Information

    1. #### Online Surveys and Polling

We may provide you with the opportunity to voluntarily complete surveys, which may be collected by an authorized third-party. If you do not wish to participate in a survey, simply decline to participate when asked.

    2. #### Advertisements on Our Website

We may display advertisements on our Website. By knowing a little about you, we will be able to deliver more relevant advertisements and content to you in the form of targeted content. We may also use third-party advertising servers to display advertisements linked to certain search terms that you have entered, or to certain pages that you are viewing. We may share aggregated data with advertisers. We may also use advertising partners to assist us in delivering personalized on-line advertisements to you through the use of cookies while you are on the Internet.

    3. #### Newsletters, Promotional E-mails and Personalized On-line Advertisements

We may offer newsletters, promotional e-mails, and personalized on-line advertisements as a service to our customers. We may send you newsletters and e-mails periodically listing current special Listing Items. You may â€œopt-out,â€ or unsubscribe from our newsletters, emails, or personalized on-line advertisements by following any unsubscribe instructions in any e-mail, newsletter, or personalized on-line advertisement you receive from us, or by sending an e-mail to info@panjo.com and asking to opt out. Opting out may take up to six weeks to remove you from the database. If you have opted out of receiving all newsletters, all promotional emails, or all personalized on-line advertisements, you will not receive future promotional emails, newsletters or personalized on-line advertisements (as applicable), unless you otherwise subsequently sign up to receive newsletters, emails, or personalized on-line advertisements. Please Note: If you receive e-mails separately from third-party merchants, then all information that you choose to disclose to them will be subject to their privacy policy, terms of use, and opt- out procedures.

    4. #### Tracking Usage

We may track customers' traffic patterns throughout their online session, including which pages, information, and advertisements a customer views while using our Website and what Listing Items they view and/or purchase. We may use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our Website, and to gather demographic information. We may share aggregated statistics about pages viewed on our Website, sales, and other shopping information with third-parties.

      1. #### Cookies

We may use cookies and may allow other third-parties to use cookies in the operation of our Website. A cookie is an industry-standard small file placed on your computer. Cookies allow us to â€œremember youâ€ when you return to the Website to make your visits more relevant and to retrieve information from your prior visits. The cookie stores information about the searches that you have made and the items that you have viewed and allows us and other third-parties to replace non-relevant advertisements with ones that are more relevant to your presumed interests. You may delete cookies on your computer; however, if you enjoy the convenience of the Website remembering you, you are advised not to delete your cookies. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you.

      2. #### Web Beacons

We may use and allow others to use web beacons in the operation of our Website. A web beacon is an industry-standard, often transparent graphic image usually no larger than a 1x1 pixel that is placed on the Website. Web beacons allow us to track responses or actions by users who view certain advertisements and to count the number of times that users visit the pages of our Website and may be used by both us and third-parties for the purpose of providing personalized media, determining which advertisements are most effective on our Website, and for targeting future advertising campaigns. We may also include web beacons in email messages or promotional newsletters for detecting whether the messages have been opened or if you performed any actions after opening them.

    5. #### Marketing Partners, Co-Branded Services, and Third-Party Websites

We may run promotions for merchants where you may visit a third-party merchant website. In some of those promotions, a window or frame containing the merchant's website may appear. Any time you are in such a window, you should assume that your personal information is being collected, used and disclosed in accordance with that merchant's policies. This Policy does not apply to information that you supply to those merchants. Any information that you share with them will be used and disclosed in accordance with that merchant's privacy policy. However, once you click on a link to return to our Website, you can expect that further information that you disclose will be treated in accordance with this Policy.

Please be aware that our Website may contain links to other websites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third-parties. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our Website are not covered by this Policy. These other websites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Additionally, other companies or ad servers, which place advertising on our Website, may collect information about you through the use of cookies when you view or click on their advertising. You should contact advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.

    6. #### Security

In order to most efficiently serve you, the purchase of Listing Items utilizing credit card transactions may be handled by established third-party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They may receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order, if applicable.

We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use your Personally Identifiable Information. The Website has industry-standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control, and we make good faith efforts to store your Personally Identifiable Information in a secure operating environment. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be absolutely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. If we provide you with a user name and password to access portions of the Website, we disclaim any responsibility for a breach of privacy as a result of your willingly or inadvertently disclosing your user name and password to others.

    7. #### Updating and Correcting Information

We believe that you should have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information you provide us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information on your Panjo Account. We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on the Website. In addition, your information, even if deleted from a current database, may still exist within an archived database, as we periodically backup information.

    8. #### Opting Out or Choosing Not to Provide Information

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, although it may be required to engage in a certain activity on the Website.

As a condition of creating a User Account and Profile with Panjo, we may on occasion send you Administrative and Promotional emails. We will send you information regarding your account activity, purchases, as well as updates about our products and promotional offers. You cannot opt-out of Administrative Emails. "Administrative Emails" relate to a User's activity on the Website, and include emails regarding a particular User's account, requests or inquiries, and purchases of Listing Items.

You may, however, opt out of Promotional Emails. Promotional Emails advertise Listing Items including exclusive sales and other offers, and/or the products and services of our Advertisers and Affiliates. If you do not want to receive Promotional Emails from us, you may elect to opt-out of receiving Promotional Emails at any time after registering by e-mailing us at info@panjo.com or by hitting the â€œunsubscribeâ€ button at the bottom of any of our e-mails, or by opting out of Promotional Emails within your User Account.

    9. #### Acceptance of Terms

By using our Website, you consent to our collection and use of this information in accordance with the terms set forth in this Policy.

  4. ### Privacy Issues

    1. #### Children's Privacy

This Website site is intended for use by persons over the age of 18. We do not seek to collect information about children under the age of 18. No information should be submitted to or posted on this Website by users under 18 years of age. We encourage parents to take an active role in their children's use of the Internet, and to inform them of the potential dangers of providing information about themselves over the Internet. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 18 years of age and believe that he or she has disclosed Personally Identifiable Information to us, please contact us at info@panjo.com so that we may delete the child's information.

    2. #### Connecting Via Social Media

Facebook: Panjo allows users to access Facebook to interact with friends and to share Listing Items on Facebook. If you are logged into Panjo and Facebook, you may merge your profiles. By proceeding you are allowing Panjo to access your information and you are agreeing to the Facebook Terms of Use in your use of the Panjo Website. Other Social Media: You may also connect to Panjo and share Listing Items from Panjo on other Social Media websites. By sharing content from Panjo on those websites, you agree to the Terms of Use for those Social Media websites.

    3. #### International Users

Our Website is accessible around the world. By visiting the Website and providing your information, you acknowledge and agree that your information can be stored for the purposes identified in this Policy. We process and store your information in North America and your information may be stored on servers located outside your residential jurisdiction and which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own. If you access the Website from outside the United States, your usage of the Website constitutes consent to the transfer of your data outside of your country and to North America.

    4. #### California Residents

California law permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third-parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to info@panjo.com or write to us at: Interactive Innovation group, Inc. (d/b/a Panjo), 820 Broadway, Santa Monica, CA 90401.

  5. ### Contacting Us

If you have any comments or questions, you may send an e-mail to info@panjo.com or write to us at: Interactive Innovation Group, Inc. (d/b/a Panjo), 820 Broadway, Santa Monica, CA 90401.
